{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Masterson",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Peter Masterson",
    "human_readable": "The name of Peter Masterson is Peter Masterson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864363074302673,
            "question": "Is Peter Masterson's name Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9801787734031677,
            "question": "What is the name of Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9737788438796997,
            "question": "Does Peter Masterson go by the name Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8404391407966614,
            "question": "Why is it important to know Peter Masterson's name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145536780357361,
            "question": "Is there anything else known about Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7478215098381042,
            "question": "Could you provide an example of a situation where knowing Peter Masterson's name would be helpful?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7467181086540222,
            "question": "How would you describe Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6844062209129333,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6770163774490356,
            "question": "What is the significance of this statement about Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6023139953613281,
            "question": "What can you infer from the statement about Peter Masterson?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Peter Masterson is Peter Masterson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6412_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of this statement about Peter Masterson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6412_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Peter Masterson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6412_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Peter Masterson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6412_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6412_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate any more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided do not consistently report Peter Masterson's birth name as Carlos, but also mention that he was known as Peter because his father preferred that name. However, there is no information to suggest that Peter Masterson was ever actually named anything other than Peter."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Peter Masterson, confirming that his name was indeed Peter Masterson."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "He was originally named Carlos Masterson.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}